agatagrudzinski.com 2012-05-04

# Presenting Featured Properties prepared by Agata Grudzinski - Destin Real Estate

 At agatagrudzinski.com ("WEBSITE") we know you care about your personal privacy and about the TERMS AND CONDITIONS that govern your use of our web site or service (the "Service"). Because we are dedicated to serving your needs and respecting your preferences, we have adopted the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. By accessing or using the Service, you ("You" or "Your" as applicable) are bound by the notices, terms and conditions in this Privacy Policy.

**How We Use the Information We Collect  
**WEBSITE offers a Real Estate Services to benefit you, including personalized property searches. WEBSITE collects and retains information about you only when we believe it will help us provide you with the services and products that you desire.

**Who We Share Information With**  
WEBSITE does not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others. We will only share your Personal Information with those vendors and affiliated companies who are acting on our behalf to serve you. Such WEBSITE vendors and affiliated companies are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data.

**What information is collected from me?**  
For each visitor to our Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes only the visitor's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).  
The information we collect consists of the following:  
1\. The domain name (but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page).  
2\. Aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit.  
3\. User-specific information on what pages visitors access or visit.  
4\. The e-mail addresses of those visitors who communicate with us via e-mail.  
5\. Information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.  
The information we collect is used only to improve the content of our Web site and to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor.

Additionally, WEBSITE uses Cookies to:  
1\. Store visitors preferences.  
2\. Record session information, such as items that visitors add to their user profile.  
Such information is collected so that WEBSITE may customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

 **Information Security and Quality  
**WEBSITE complies with all state and federal restrictions and regulations relating to the use of customer information. WEBSITE has put in place appropriate technical and managerial procedures to keep your personally identifiable information accurate, complete, current and secure.

**Scope of This Privacy Policy**  
This privacy policy only applies to agatagrudzinski.com. The site contains links to sites operated and maintained by third parties over which we have absolutely no control. Please be aware that these sites may collect information about you, and operate according to their own privacy practices that may differ from this privacy policy. Remember that once you are outside the agatagrudzinski.com website, any information you submit is outside of our control.

**Consent  
**When you provide us with Personal Information, you consent to the collection and use of this information by WEBSITE. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Change/Removal**  
We need your help in making sure your personal information is correct in our systems. Please notify us at contact[at]agatagrudzinski.com of changes to your name, address, title, phone number or email address. You may correct your personal information by changing your user profile or you may elect via return email not to receive future WEBSITE contacts (i.e. mailings, calls, etc.). In the event you elect not to receive any future contacts from WEBSITE, we will remove your name from all of our contact lists; however, WEBSITE can only promise to remove you from any lists we control.  
**Questions Regarding the Privacy Policy**  
If You have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or any concern about privacy at agatagrudzinski.com or the use of the Service, please contact us by calling (800) 657-0650 or email at contact[at]agatagrudzinski.com
